Guide to the Thain White Papers 1877-1983
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula,
- Photographs, 1877-1976; Series VIII; 2.75 linear feet; 758 photographs
  - General, 1889-1979; Subseries 1; 1.25 linear feet; 366 photos
    - 102A "Deaths Point", undated; 137(VIII):125
    - Pit 100 looking down coulee towards Snake Creek, undated; 137(VIII):126
    - Four fired brass, copper primers, undated; 137(VIII):127
    - Bullets, Battle of the Bear's Paw, undated; 137(VIII):128
    - Three fired bullets, undated; 137(VIII):129
    - Bill Parsons, inside a barricade, Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):130
    - Looking south, Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):131
    - Looking south, Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):132
    - Looking southeast, Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):133
    - Looking southwest, Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):134
    - Looking east, Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):135
    - Looking west, Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):136
    - Looking southwest from southern edge of Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):137
    - Looking east along northern perimeter of the boulder barricades, undated; 137(VIII):138
    - Looking northwest, Lawyers Canyon in distance and site of Fort Misery School in right, undated; 137(VIII):139
    - Looking to the top of Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):140
    - Relics from Misery Hill - Nez Perce War, undated; 137(VIII):141
    - Jay Marshall (left) and Laune Harvey studying a map, exploration of Nez Perce Trail, 1975; 137(VIII):142
    - Marshall (left), Harvey (center), and John ? inspecting increment boring samples of a Douglas Fir, exploration of Nez Perce Trail, 1975; 137(VIII):143
    - Marshall (left), Harvey (center), and John ? Inspecting increment boring samples of a Douglas Fir, exploration of Nez Perce Trail, 1975; 137(VIII):144
    - Marshall (left), Harvey and John ? inspecting a Ponderosa Pine, exploration of Nez Perce Trail, 1975; 137(VIII):145
    - Rise of rock, exploration of Nez Perce Trail, 1975; 137(VIII):146
    - Old Indian canoe, (copy), undated; 137(VIII):147
    - Kalispell type canoe, from Pacific Northwest Indian Center, 1930; 137(VIII):148
    - "Mandan Bull Boat," from The North American Indian, 1907-1930; 137(VIII):149
    - "A Mandan Village," photo from Plate I3 Am Oberen 1832-1834, Frankford, 1930; 137(VIII):150
    - "Kalispell Camp", undated; 137(VIII):151
    - "Kalispell Canoes", undated; 137(VIII):152
    - "Home of the Kalispell", undated; 137(VIII):153
    - "On the Pend d'Oreille", undated; 137(VIII):154
    - "Kalispell Scene", undated; 137(VIII):155
    - Two buildings, Fort Belknap, September 1960; 137(VIII):156
    - Close up of right building in 137(VIII):156, an office or living quarters, September 1960; 137(VIII):157
    - Close up of left building in 137(VIII):156, perhaps a stable, September 1960; 137(VIII):158
    - Close up of left building in 137(VIII):156, perhaps a stable, September 1960; 137(VIII):159
    - Aerial of Fort C.F. Smith site, Big Horn River, and Hayfield Fight area, 1962; 137(VIII):160
    - Marker of Fort C.F. Smith, erected 1933, 1962; 137(VIII):161
    - Looking NE toward the site of the Hayfield Fight, Fort C.F. Smith, 1962; 137(VIII):162
    - Looking N over the bank from the fort site, Fort C.F. Smith, 1962; 137(VIII):163
    - Fort C.F. Smith, looking N, 1962; 137(VIII):164
    - Fort C.F. Smith, 1962; 137(VIII):165
    - Ornamental strap worm by officers, Fort C.F. Smith, 1962; 137(VIII):166
    - small relics from Fort C.F. Smith, 1962; 137(VIII):167
    - Fort C.F. Smith memorial shaft, 1962; 137(VIII):168
    - Marker of site of Hay-Corral Battle, undated; 137(VIII):169
    - Cartridges located at the site of the Hayfield Fight, 1962; 137(VIII):170
    - Relics from Fort C.F. Smith, 1962; 137(VIII):171
    - Site of Fort Conrad 1875-1890, 1962; 137(VIII):172
    - Looking northeast to the site of Fort Conrad, 1962; 137(VIII):173
    - Lone cottonwood at James McDivitt's location, 1962; 137(VIII):175
    - Lone cottonwood where James McDivitt had his residence, 1962; 137(VIII):176
    - Relics from James McDivitt site near Fort Conrad, 1962; 137(VIII):177
    - Relics from James McDivitt site, 1962; 137(VIII):178
    - Piece of lead and flat iron, 1962; 137(VIII):179
    - Lead device with Indian head penny, 1962; 137(VIII):180
    - Lead device with Indian head penny, 1962; 137(VIII):181
    - Last of the chimney that was standing in late teens, unidentified people, photo courtesy of Everett Baker, obtained 1967, undated; 137(VIII):182
    - Everett Baker at site of the last chimney at Chimney Coulee, 1967; 137(VIII):183
    - Looking E, over Chimney Coulee, 1967; 137(VIII):184
    - Two men near the site of Chimney Coulee, 1967; 137(VIII):185
    - Site of Chimney Coulee, 1967; 137(VIII):186
    - Site of Chimney Coulee, 1967; 137(VIII):187
    - Two relics from Chimney Coulee, 1967; 137(VIII):188
    - Chimney Coulee looking SE, 1974; 137(VIII):189
    - Chimney Coulee artifacts, 1974; 137(VIII):190
    - Chimney Coulee marker, 1975; 137(VIII):191
    - Fort Walch, Wood Mountain Trail marker, 1975; 137(VIII):192
    - Medicine Rock as it looks today, 1960; 137(VIII):193
    - Medicine Rock as it looks today, 1960; 137(VIII):194
    - Old Indian trail at "Shinkoots Rock", 1960; 137(VIII):195
    - Old log cabin that served as a stage stop from 1890s to circa 1910, 1960; 137(VIII):196
    - Portion of the map accompanying Volume XII Book I of Pacific's Railway Reports, 1968; 137(VIII):197
    - Cleared land which is a portion of the Old Farrey Ranch, 1968; 137(VIII):198
    - Location of several stone hearths, 1968; 137(VIII):199
    - Portion of "The Wagon Road to Demersville", 1968; 137(VIII):200
    - Remains of Medicine Rock after vandalized, 1968; 137(VIII):201
    - An invitation to the editor of the Inter Lake to attend the execution of four Indians in 1890, copy from D.C. Johns collection, 137(VIII):202
    - Wagon road near where J.M. Dunn was murdered, 1962; 137(VIII):203
    - Fired .45 cartridge that was located at the site where Pascale killed J.M. Dunn, 1962; 137(VIII):204
    - Painting of Charley Reevis, by Sam Whipprud, circa 1952; 137(VIII):205
    - Possible site of Spring Hill Stage Station, 1971; 137(VIII):206
    - Political Hill perch, undated; 137(VIII):213
    - Bull's Place perch #1, west side of US Highway 93, near Lakeside, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):214
    - Bull's Place perch #2, undated; 137(VIII):215
    - Bull's Place perch #3, undated; 137(VIII):216
    - Bull's Place perch #4, undated; 137(VIII):217
    - Bull's Place perch #4, undated; 137(VIII):218
    - Crobb's Orchard perch, undated; 137(VIII):219
    - Crobb's Orchard perch, undated; 137(VIII):220
    - Bill Keseler's Honey and Pear tree, undated; 137(VIII):221
    - Deer perch, No. 1, Jack Fisher's Ranch, undated; 137(VIII):222
    - Deer perch, No. 2, Jack Fisher's Ranch, undated; 137(VIII):223
    - Deer perch, No. 3, Jack Fisher's Ranch, undated; 137(VIII):224
    - Howard Glazier's Deer perch, undated; 137(VIII):225
    - Perch on Glenn McCarty's place, undated; 137(VIII):226
    - Buckhorn, No. 1, undated; 137(VIII):227
    - Buckhorn, No. 2, undated; 137(VIII):228
    - Buckhorn, No. 2, undated; 137(VIII):229
    - Buckhorn, No. 3, undated; 137(VIII):230
    - Remains of cabin where Buckhorn's sister cooked for logging crew; photo by Jon Hutchinson, circa 1965; 137(VIII):231
    - Portion of Elmer Koon's cabin; photo by Jon Hutchinson, circa 1968; 137(VIII):232
    - Perch, used to store grain for logging horses and to shoot deer from, undated; 137(VIII):233
    - Koon's deer perch on Lloyd Anderson's place, undated; 137(VIII):234
    - Dale Ebert's deer perch, undated; 137(VIII):235
    - Dale Ebert's deer perch, undated; 137(VIII):236
    - John Cooley's deer perch, undated; 137(VIII):237
    - Doring deer stand, west of Lakeside, Montana, 1976; 137(VIII):238
    - Chris Radel's deer stand, undated; 137(VIII):239
    - Charles Stubb's Medal, Kalispell, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):240
    - Charles Stubb's Medal, Kalispell, Montana; reverse of 137(VIII):240, undated; 137(VIII):241
    - Indian Peace Medal (1798), bronze, privately owned, undated; 137(VIII):242
    - Rifle pits of the Yellowstone wagon and prospecting expedition (1874), undated; 137(VIII):243
    - Rifle pits of the Yellowstone Wagon Road (1874), 1961; 137(VIII):244
    - Rifle pits near Rosebud Creek, 1961; 137(VIII):245
    - Relics found at the "Corral" on the Rosebud camp, undated; 137(VIII):246
    - Williams Junction, 1973; 137(VIII):247
    - Portion of map from Great Divide by Earl of Ponranen (?), (1874), undated; 137(VIII):248
    - Point of Rock Hotel and Stage Station, 1895, undated; 137(VIII):249
    - Point of Rock Hotel and Stage Station, 1895, undated; 137(VIII):250
    - Stage at Virginia City Montana, from Montana Historical Society, undated; 137(VIII):251
    - Freight road to Bannack, Medicine Lodge Road, 1973; 137(VIII):252
    - Wagon passing Shenon Hotel, undated; 137(VIII):253
    - Fort Benton Stage at Sun River, Helena (from Montana Historical Society), 1885; 137(VIII):254
    - Historical coach of the days of General Custer at the Milwaukee Station, Miles City, Montana - from Ed B. McCurdy collection, undated; 137(VIII):255
    - Stage Prickly Pear Canyon (Montana Historical Society), undated; 137(VIII):256
    - Malta Zortman Stage (Montana Historical Society), undated; 137(VIII):257
    - Unidentified mountains, undated; 137(VIII):258
    - Fort Benton Stage at 28 Mile Spring (Montana Historical Society), undated; 137(VIII):259
    - Marker for site of Fort Conrad: 1875-1890, undated; 137(VIII):260
    - Unidentified landscape, undated; 137(VIII):261
    - Junction Idaho, 1910; 137(VIII):262; Dan J. Pyeatt
    - divide to Wisdom (S?) Gibbonsville Idaho, undated; 137(VIII):263
    - Jae Mongut cabin on Big Lodge Flats near Rollins, Montana, built 1890, 1968; 137(VIII):264
    - Idaho Map, circa 1904; 137(VIII):265
    - Track repair on Gilmore S Pittsburgh RR in Idaho, (from Dorothy P. Baker), circa 1910; 137(VIII):266
    - track repair on Gilmore S Pittsburgh RR in Idaho, (from Dorothy P. Baker), circa 1910; 137(VIII):267
    - track repair on Gilmore S Pittsburgh RR in Idaho, (from Dorothy P. Baker), circa 1910; 137(VIII):268
    - Salmon City, Idaho (from Dorothy P. Baker), 1910; 137(VIII):269
    - Post office and stage office in Lemhi, Idaho (from Dorothy P. Baker), circa 1885; 137(VIII):270
    - Gilmore Mercantile Company, 1973; 137(VIII):271
    - Jaggers Hotel, Gilmore, Idaho, 1973; 137(VIII):272
    - Jaggers Hotel, Gilmore, Idaho, 1973; 137(VIII):273
    - Last freight wagon to Salmon near Lemhi, Idaho (from Baker), 1912; 137(VIII):274
    - Last freight wagon to Salmon near Lemhi, Idaho (from Baker), 1912; 137(VIII):275
    - Barn that the Red Rock - Salmon River State operated from, 1973; 137(VIII):276
    - RR, Gilmore and Pittsburgh, discontinued 1939, (from Baker), undated; 137(VIII):277
    - RR, Gilmore and Pittsburgh, discontinued 1939, (from Baker), undated; 137(VIII):278
    - RR, Gilmore and Pittsburgh, discontinued 1939, (from Baker), undated; 137(VIII):279
    - Junction of highway 29-28, Leadore, Idaho, 1973; 137(VIII):280
    - Junction of highway 29-28, Leadore, Idaho, 1973; 137(VIII):281
    - Monida-Yellowstone Stage Co., Barn at Monida, circa 1898; 137(VIII):282
    - Red Rock Pass, 1973; 137(VIII):283
    - Old barn, Yellowstone - Monida Stage Co., Monida, 1971; 137(VIII):284
    - Dipping oat of Beardsley Bros., west end of Pine Butte, 1973; 137(VIII):285
    - Artifacts from site of Pine Butte Stage Station, 1971; 137(VIII):286
    - Artifacts from site of Pine Butte Stage Station, 1971; 137(VIII):287
    - Artifacts from site of Pine Butte Stage Station, 1971; 137(VIII):288
    - Somers to Polson Stage, 1911; 137(VIII):289
    - Stage over Flathead Indian Reservation, 1911; 137(VIII):290
    - Ravalli - Polson Stage, near St. Ignatius, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):291
    - Allard Stage Line(McKay photo), circa 1910; 137(VIII):292
    - Charlie Allard's Ranch(John's collection), circa 1906; 137(VIII):293
    - John Weightman Livery Stable, built early 1900s, undated; 137(VIII):294
    - Charlie Allard's Ranch, 1973; 137(VIII):295
    - Stage between Ravalli and Polson, Montana, 1906; 137(VIII):296
    - Polson - Ravalli Stage, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):297
    - Ravalli Hotel, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):298
    - Passenger stage, 1912; 137(VIII):299
    - Will Hamer's house, Somers, Montana, built 1891, 1970; 137(VIII):300
    - Williams Stage to Ronan-Ravalli, 1911; 137(VIII):301
    - Stage coach Polson - Ravalli, Montana, 1909-10; 137(VIII):302
    - Map of Flathead Indian Reservation in 1908, undated; 137(VIII):303
    - J. Dooley's first post office-Flathead Salish (Theirault Svore photo), undated; 74-230
    - Big Arm, Montana, undated; 74-231
    - Buffalo skull and bones on Montana Plains, undated; 81-37
    - Sheepherders wagon and scenic butte on Montana Plains, undated; 81-38
    - Carriage on Montana Plains, undated; 81-39
    - Stockyard, horse, and wagon, and sheepherders wagon, undated; 81-40
    - Buffalo skull on Montana Plains, undated; 81-41
    - Ranch North of Fort Peck Indian Reservation, Montana (Fred Long Ranch), 1905-1907; 81-43
    - Ed White on horse, 1905-1907; 81-44
    - Surveyor's camp on Fort Peck Indian Reservation, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-45
    - Cook house, shearer's camp, J.B. Long Co., 1905-1907; 81-46
    - Evanson's sod barn, 1905-1907; 81-47
    - First winter on the Ringling & White Sulphur Springs line, 1905-1906; 81-50
    - First winter on the Ringling & White Sulphur Springs line, 1905-1906; 81-51
    - Carriage at foot of Hope's Hill, Lakeside, Montana, 1901; 81-52
    - Stagecoach between Polson and Ravalli, 1901; 81-53
    - Lone Indian camp, little heroin with axe, (woman in camp refused to have photo taken), undated; 81-54.1
    - Surveyor's camp on Fort Peck Indian Reservation, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-55
    - Surveyor on fort Peck Indian Reservation, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-56
    - Surveyors on fort Peck Indian Reservation, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-57
    - Surveyors on fort Peck Indian Reservation, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-58
    - Surveyors on fort Peck Indian Reservation, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-59
    - Camp outfit and sheep-taken at sunrise, J.B. Long Co., 1905-1907; 81-61
    - Nester's shack near Nashua, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-70
    - Indian home Frazer, Montana-only eating place in Frazer, 1907; 81-71
    - Ranch north of Fort Peck Indian Reservation, J.B. Long Co., 1905-1907; 81-72
    - Hotel Shannon, Glasgow, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-73
    - Glasgow, Montana, Main Street, 1905-1907; 81-74
    - Glasgow, Montana-Court House and school, 1905-1907; 81-75
    - Dugout just off Fort Peck Indian Reservation, west of Poplar Creek near Scobey, Montana. "Dutch Henry" and his gang holed up here, 1907; 81-76
    - James Deegan Store, Frazer, Montana, 1907 "Sod busters" place, 9 miles southwest of Scobey, Montana, 1907-1908; 81-77
    - Dan Knopp's store, Oswego, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-79
    - Sheepherder's camp outfit, Shorty and Jack, 1905-1907; 81-80
    - Sheepherder's camp outfit, 1905-1907; 81-81
    - Shearing pens at Frazer, Montana, J.B. Long Co., 1907-1908; 81-82
    - J.B. Long home ranch on Teton River, north Great Falls, 1905-1907; 81-83
    - J.B. Long home ranch on Teton River, north Great Falls, 1905-1907; 81-84
    - J.B. Long home camp, 1905-1907; 81-85
    - Herman Yeaton, chore boy, at home ranch washing clothes, J.B. Long Co., circa 1910; 81-86
    - Sheepherder's wagon, 1905-1907; 81-88
    - Sheepherder's wagon, camps are very heavy and are blocked up, the running gear is used to drive to townsite, 1905-1907; 81-89
    - Sheepherder's wagon and camp, 1905-1907; 81-90
    - Sheepherder's wagon and camp (back from town), 1905-1907; 81-91
    - Sheepherder's wagon and camp, and E. White's horse; J.B. Long Co., 1905-1907; 81-92
    - Hotel Shannon and new sewer pipe, Glasgow, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-93
    - Shearers in front of cook house, man on right is deaf and dumb, 1905-1907; 81-94
    - Sheep crossing, Lisma's Ferry on Missouri River, 7,000 head took 1.5 days, 100 head at a time, 1907; 81-95
    - Frank Dernback and Roanie, sheepherder's wagon and camp, J.B. Long Ranch, 1908-1909; 81-96
    - Frank Dernback and Roanie, sheepherder's wagon and camp, J.B. Long Ranch, 1908-1909; 81-97
    - Carload of wool hauled about 50 miles, undated; 81-98
    - Timmon's residence at Scobey, Montana, undated; 81-101
    - Main Street, White Sulphur Springs, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-102
    - White Sulphur Springs, Montana, horse pulling sleigh, 1905-1907; 81-103
    - Heading to camp with load of cow chips, Long Livestock Co., Teton range, north of Great Falls, 1905; 81-104
    - "Sod buster's" house near Scobey, Montana, at head of Police Creek, 1907; 81-108
    - Wagons on rail car-new tops on wagons ready to follow sheep to Oswego, Montana, from Fort Benton, Montana. Photo by: Ernest White, 1908-1910; 81-109
    - Indian town on the Missouri River bottom, Deer Hills far across river, undated; 81-113
    - J.B. Long Ranch, 1905-1907; 81-114
    - Sheep wagons, Browning, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-115
    - Sheep wagons, Browning, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-116
    - Sheep wagons, Browning, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-117
    - Sheep wagons, Browning, Montana, 1905-1907; 81-118
    - Snyder Hotel on Lake McDonald, 1960; 83-43
  - Boats and Planes, 1905-1982; Subseries 2; 0.4 linear feet; 131 photos
    This subseries contains photographs related to White's research and writing on various boats and planes.
    - Man on a ferry on Flathead Lake, undated; 137(VIII):304
    - Steamboat Crescent on Flathead Lake, undated; 137(VIII):305
    - Ferry on Flathead Lake, June 5, 1982; 137(VIII):306
    - Freightboat Helena(steam operated), built by Kehoe and Gagnon, circa 1917; 137(VIII):307
    - New Klondike on Flathead Lake, undated; 137(VIII):308
    - Scene at Big Arm, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):309
    - A boat called DeSmet on a bridge, undated; 137(VIII):310
    - S.S. Grant built about 1885, used by territorial government and operated as a passenger boat for a short time. Quit about 1890., circa 1885-1890; 137(VIII):311
    - S.S. Bigfork, later called Somers of Polson, built at Bigfork, Montana by Captain Anderson of Somers, Montana, circa 1907-1908; 137(VIII):312
    - Paul Bunyan in a dock, undated; 137(VIII):313
    - Unidentified steamboat on a lake, undated; 137(VIII):314
    - S.S. Hodge II on a lake, undated; 137(VIII):315
    - Kootenai in dock, undated; 137(VIII):316
    - Unidentified boat at Somers, Montana, with a crowd of people on it, undated; 137(VIII):317
    - Star at Woods Bay on point with Ray Newton, 1936; undated; 137(VIII):318
    - Cassie D with a group of people standing on it, possibly at Glacier Park, undated; 137(VIII):319
    - S.S. Hodge I in dock, undated; 137(VIII):320
    - Defiance in dock, undated; 137(VIII):321
    - Frank Bird Linderman standing on Doman, undated; 137(VIII):322
    - unidentified boat on lake during the Winter, undated; 137(VIII):323
    - ABC docked at Melita Island, undated; 137(VIII):324
    - International in dock, undated; 137(VIII):325
    - Pile of wood near Terry, undated; 137(VIII):326
    - Steamboat Klondyke with passengers, undated; 137(VIII):327
    - Group of kids sitting on a group of ships, undated; 137(VIII):328
    - City of Dixon (Steamboat) in dock with 2 men standing on board, 1912; 137(VIII):329
    - City of Polson(Steamboat) in dock during with a group of men standing on board, 1912; 137(VIII):330
    - Two men standing in front of an airplane with a boat in the background, undated; 137(VIII):331
    - Men unloading an oil rig, undated; 137(VIII):332
    - Men unloading an oil rig, undated; 137(VIII):333
    - Polson, Montana, steam ferry, undated; 137(VIII):334
    - Large group of people standing on board a ship, undated; 137(VIII):335
    - Jamming on the Ice-people standing on docks near Polson on Flathead Lake, undated; 137(VIII):336
    - Klondyke in dock, undated; 137(VIII):337
    - Boats of some kind being hauled by trucks across land, undated; 137(VIII):338
    - Group of people standing on the "the speed boat of them all' the City of Polson, undated; 137(VIII):339
    - Steamboat steaming through the narrows of Flathead Lake, undated; 137(VIII):340
    - Group of people sitting on a Steamboat, undated; 137(VIII):341
    - New Klondyke Excursion at Yellow Bay, undated; 137(VIII):342
    - Men standing around some docked smaller ships, undated; 137(VIII):343
    - Group of wagons and horses gathered around a docked ship, undated; 137(VIII):344
    - Group of people sitting aboard a ship, undated; 137(VIII):345
    - the Klondyke on Flathead Lake with a few men standing on it, undated; 137(VIII):346
    - Montana docked at Dayton, Montana, circa 1911; 137(VIII):347
    - Cassie D docked at Lake McDonald with a group of men sitting on it, undated; 137(VIII):348
    - Klondyke on a Lake, undated; 137(VIII):349
    - a man standing aboard the Paul Bunyan, undated; 137(VIII):350
    - Unidentified steamship on an unidentified lake, undated; 137(VIII):351
    - Unidentified steamship on an unidentified lake, undated; 137(VIII):352
    - Man on Paul Bunyan, undated; 137(VIII):353
    - Man on Paul Bunyan, undated; 137(VIII):354
    - Man on Paul Bunyan, undated; 137(VIII):355
    - Man on Paul Bunyan, undated; 137(VIII):356
    - Large crowd of people gathered around the Klondike, undated; 137(VIII):357
    - Group of people gathered around unidentified ship, undated; 137(VIII):358
    - People in a car during a parade, undated; 137(VIII):359
    - Montana on Flathead Lake, circa 1910; 137(VIII):360
    - Montana in dock, undated; 137(VIII):361
    - Montana in dock, from a distance, undated; 137(VIII):362
    - People using the Demersville Ferry to cross a river, circa 1887; 137(VIII):363
    - Montana, undated; 137(VIII):364
    - People preparing a ferry to sail, undated; 137(VIII):365
    - Ship preparing to make a mainland landing near Melita Island, undated; 137(VIII):366
    - Men driving a truck into water to unload some type of ferry, undated; 137(VIII):367
    - People on a group of boats with a ferry nearby, undated; 137(VIII):368
    - Group of men sitting on a houseboat, undated; 137(VIII):369
    - Convention of Montana Banners' Association near Polson, Montana, on Klondike Excursion, June 7, 1920; 137(VIII):370
    - Aerial, unidentified group of buildings near a lake, undated; 137(VIII):371
    - Aerial, unidentified group of buildings near a lake, undated; 137(VIII):372
    - Montana on dry land with a few men standing on it, undated; 137(VIII):373
    - Dock near Somers, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):374; Previously assigned photo number 74-255
    - People on a dock in Dayton, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):375
    - Group of men sitting on the Ballard, undated; 137(VIII):376
    - The Howard James, undated; 137(VIII):377
    - Demersville on lake, circa 1915; 137(VIII):378
    - Demersville on lake, circa 1915; 137(VIII):379
    - Skinkoots coming towards a dock, undated; 137(VIII):380
    - Paul Bunyan from a distance, undated; 137(VIII):381
    - Group of people standing aboard The New Klondike, undated; 137(VIII):382
    - Klondike from a distance, undated; 137(VIII):383
    - Klondike in a dock, undated; 137(VIII):384
    - Side of the Klondike, undated; 137(VIII):385
    - Ferry or oil rig preparing to go on the water, undated; 137(VIII):386
    - Ship about to dock near Polson, Montana, 1908; 137(VIII):387